Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his triumph, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
From far away, he was led by the path of the world.
The path of the world is broken.
You can't do it, everybody get down.
You can't do it, step up, step up.
Oh oh.
運命の凍らに I'm falling down
君と彼女のハーモニー
生まれ過去に置き去りのまま
君の強気の香りは
丸心に引きずったまま
待ってるだけじゃも足りない
Take through it now
真っ赤に抱きしめ
明日しだスルエイ
Take through it now
光灯して
真っ暗なメイロイ
Take through it now
La la la la la la la
La la la la la la
Take through it now
La la la la la la la
目の前の希望掴まって
There was one more piece of information
The Midnight Sun members revealed during their questioning
Asta?
Remember the hideout they took you to after you were captured?
And the mysterious stone tablet that was hidden there?
That thing?
According to our captives
They call the gems embedded in that tablet magic stones
They believe that gathering them will allow them to be reborn into their true forms
With close ties to the mana
Thereby granting them immense power
Four stones remain to be gathered
And from what our captives said
It seems they know the location of one of them
Hmm, where's that?
The underwater temple
One of the strong magic regions
So, we have to get there before this
Eye of the Midnight Sun does
And make off with this magic stone thingy
Is that the general idea?
That's right, and I believe the best people for this mission will be found in the Black Bulls
Who are unique among the Magic Knights
Because of the number of its members unfettered by family or social standing
So, will you do it?
Looks like you didn't make it to the main dish
Rest in peace
For saving the underwater temple and its people, you have my gratitude
Thank you
Thank you so much
All right
Got it
And now our mission's complete
Listen up, gang
Nice work
Having been assigned a crucial mission by the Wizard King
The Black Bulls won a fierce battle against a terrible foe
Secured the magic stone
And returned home with all members present and accounted for
You did such a great job, everybody!
You're the one who wound up the most seriously injured
So...exhausted
Hello, my angel
Your big brother has completed his mission and returned to dry land
I feel so much better just knowing you're breathing the same air again
Oh, that seafood was delicious
My god, no good stomach, get for me
There's nothing more satisfying than the first bottle or three after finishing a big job
Completing an important mission like this is a win for the whole squad
Something this big should improve our standing
Well, what do you know, guys?
Guess it turns out we're not utterly hopeless after all
True, we've gotten better
But considering our record, we're still dead last out of all the Magic Knight squads
Wait a second
Huh?
He wasn't with us, was he?
Oh, crap
I completely forgot about Gordon
Hey, somebody talk to him
He looks kind of depressed
Nah, he's ticked off
Just listen to the way he's mumbling
I'm not so sure, isn't Gordon always mumbling?
It's creepy never having any idea what's going through his head
Gordon Agrippa
A lonely fellow who only wants friends but just can't seem to make them
Looks like we're here either
Huh?
Don't cherish the memory of them forever
Okay, I get to go give our report to the Wizard King
Aught to be fun
Charmy, you go grab the prisoners and come too
Will I get a tree for God with me?
Nope
Finral, portal duty
Will there be pretty girls?
There won't
Aww
Marie is a perfect angel
I want to go with you, Captain!
Please take me!
You know, you're a little too much of a go-getter sometimes
The main thing you should be worried about right now is resting and getting yourself healed up
Not that I'm even the tiniest bit worried about you or anything, because I'm not
Just do whatever
What was that for, Noelle?
Given those gnarly wounds of yours, you'd be better off staying put
Although honestly, if I want to be fair, you were with me when the Wizard King gave us the mission in the first place
So alright, I guess you can go
Awesome!
As for the rest of you, get some sleep
See you've got that covered
Oh, hey Nero, you're tagging along too?
That reminds me, I've been wondering about something
That shiny thing you found back in Saucy Village kind of looked like the magic stone we got from the temple
Asuka!
Uh, yeah?
Come on, we're about to leave
Quit your dilly-dallying
Sorry, Captain Yumi
Wow, it's just as crazy big as ever
Shut up
Okay, Finral, thanks for giving us a ride
Huh?
We'll see you when it's time to head back
Hey!
That's not fair!
I want to meet the Wizard King!
I thought I'd prove I could be more than just your chauffeur
Although, if I'm choosing between meeting with the Wizard King and flirting with the local ladies
Actually, I'm good, see ya!
Never fear lovelies, Finral's coming!
I see
So they did send someone to retrieve the stone from the temple
And you said that he was a member of the Third Eye?
That's right, the one they call Vetter the Despair
Sounds like a fitting title
We'll examine the body here
And interrogate the Midnight Sun minions you captured
You scum!
Yeah, okay
Your binding magic is truly outstanding
That fluff is surprisingly strong
And who are you, Oka?
Wow, Yumi, I didn't know you had a child
Look how big she is, though
When did this happen?
Whoa, not mine
Hey mister, do you have any yummy treats for me?
Look, just drop it
Whoa!
Oh, safe
Here you go, one magic stone as ordered
Hmm
Thank you for this
I know it wasn't easy to procure
You've probably heard
But there were many casualties among the magic knights who fought in Rockway
Now they can rest in peace
You did receive your share of injuries
But the Black Bulls completed this critical mission without losing a single member
That's nothing short of marvelous
And somewhere along the line
You grew stronger yourself
Yumi
I understand you've made that foreigner a magic knight
Honestly, what is Captain Julius thinking?
Making someone like him a magic knight captain?
Has the Wizard King gone mad?
You're kind of weird, aren't you, mister?
You've done well
I'm so proud of the amazing magic knight captain you've become
Truly
I'm 28, not 12, so cut it out, will you?
You're embarrassing me
Yes, of course, sorry about that
Tell me if you remember this little quote
If you want to say you're right, get results from doing things your way
Well, Julius
Those were your words
Just like I told you before we left
I accepted that mission to prove that you weren't wrong
That you hadn't made any mistakes
The way they fought against that monster back in the underwater temple
My squad members proved that I wasn't wrong either
Yes
And Asta
You've had another impressive showing, young man
You're doing well
Very well, in fact
I expect we'll see a lot more from you
Thank you, sir
Um, there was something I was wondering
I know you're super busy
And I don't want to bother you
But I was hoping that maybe
Of course, what is it?
Well, if it isn't too much trouble
Sir, could I have your autograph, please?
Please
Tell you what, you can have mine on your face
No, please
Thank you
Don't be nervous around me for-
Please forgive the intrusion, sir, but it's important
Hey, Mushroom Head
I've told you before, it's-
You know what? Never mind
Now's not the time for this
Go on, Marks, what is it?
It's Kitan, a border village in sight of frequent skirmishes with the Diamonds Kingdom
A Diamond Unit is attacking it as we speak
Of course, they had to strike now
So many
Whoa!
That looks like a whole army of them!
This is a far cry from our usual skirmishing
Especially when you consider those who appear to be in command
Yes
Lagas
Brox
And Yagos
Three of the eight Shining Generals
The eight Shining Generals? I've never heard of them before
They're the eight most powerful people in the whole Diamond Kingdom
You might think of them as being kind of like our Magic Knight Captains
That's super not good
Worse
Kitan is the linchpin of our Border Defense
If we lose it, we'll be wide open to a Diamond Kingdom invasion
The time has come
This battle could alter the course of the Diamond Kingdom's history
A big battle, it's been far too long
How very exciting
We'll crush these Clover Kingdom weaklings and take their precious Border Town
The little maggots don't stand a chance
Our spies informed us that the Clover Kingdom had been worn down by the continued conflict with the Eye of the Midnight Sun
And that Border Security was then on the ground as a result
It seems they were correct
We just need to take control of Kitan and then we'll have the upper hand
Let's get started already
This area has a wealth of resources too
The fact that's lost on those Clover Kingdom fools
Prepare yourselves
The Diamond Kingdom is attacking
On your honor as Magic Knights
Prevent their invasion at any cost
Sir!
Deploy the Magic Barrier
I have 50 mages pouring their magic power into this barrier
You aren't going to break through it easily
None of your attacks will be able to reach us
But our attacks can pass through without a problem
Our first target is that Lightning Magic Wielder
Logus
Pick him up
Give up
Is that feeble little attack the best you people could muster?
Fine then
I'll show you how her proper offensive spell is done
Lightning Creation Magic
Thunderbird Warrior Air Splitting Magic Faux Gear
Well that was easy
Now we charge in and take him down
Ha ha ha
Move quickly but don't break formation
Everyone keep to your 10 troop platoon
Defense mages deploy barrier magic while watching for long distance spells
Sir!
Close and mid-range attack mages I want you to store up your power as you scout for the enemy
Long-range attack mages maintain a barrage of low-cost spells to keep the defenders on their toes
Sir!
And for the final stage of our attack
Red Clay Creation Magic
Raging Great War Tau
Ah!
Ha ha ha!
Long live the Diamond Kingdom
Dammit, Brox, you reckless idiot
I wasn't done yet
A general should stay out of the fray and give orders
Not charge in ahead of his troops
Where is your dignity, man?
Oh, he always does that
It lacks polish, true
But it does demoralize the enemy
And that's what he's after
You can't deny he's got a talent for it
Come, Yagos
Let's press the attack, shall we?
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Ha ha ha ha!
It's no use!
The attacks are too much!
Not good
Hmm
Kaijin's defense is shattered
They're in serious trouble
No kidding
Wait, hold on
Is that-
What now?
Speak, Mushroom Head
It's them
They came
Huh?
The mightiest magic knight squad in the Clover Kingdom
The Golden Dawn
Come, knights
It's time for us to show our guests
Exactly how unwelcome they are
You know
I think you're testing it
Ha ha ha!
This is what you send us back up
Only one measly magic knight captain?
That's just pathetic
Attention generals
Enemy reinforcements have arrived
Huh?
Focus your attacks on the Golden Dawn
I repeat
Focus on the Golden Dawn
Those idiots
Idiots
Do they truly believe they can defeat us with one puny squad of magic knights?
Huh?
What's this?
Some scrawny boy thinks he can stand in the way of my charge?
You fool!
I'll blast you to bits!
Wind magic
Tornado fang!
Bang!
Now, what was that about blasting me to bits?
My, my!
Look at you, Mr. Show-off
It'll be more fun if you use my power, too
This kind of cockiness is exactly why you can't ever seem to make any friends, you know
The right response would have been a pleasant chuckle, not a dismissive sneer
A pleasant chuckle?
Sure
What was that?
Well
Hey, you can't just ignore me like that
I'm one of the four great nature spirits
Say something already
Fine, something
Seriously?
At this rate, you're going to die friendless, you insufferable grouch
But don't worry, because I'm going to stay right by your side every step of the way
Even if you are an ungrateful lot with inexcusably bad manners
Now, if you get rid of all these pests, you can celebrate by taking me out on a nice date
Yeah, right
You don't look very excited
You weren't planning to turn me down, are you?
Whoa
Ha ha ha
I'm glad to see they brought someone who actually has a backbone
I pray the provisions prevailed
It looks like he's fielding the wind spirit
I'm dying to see her in person
Yuno's power certainly seems to be increasing
Swiftly
Great job, you jerk
The Golden Dawn will help even things up a little bit
But the enemy still has three generals and many more troops
I'd like to send reinforcements, but I'm not even certain who we have available
Neither am I, sir
The Golden Dawn will help even things up a little bit
But the enemy still has three generals and many more troops
I'd like to send reinforcements, but I'm not even certain who we have available
Neither am I, sir
The Curtin Lions are in the Yoto Mountains
And the Silver Eagles are tied up with the Smay Kingdom
There's a simple solution
You can send me
I'm your best option
I think Fenril's been to that village before so I can get there quick
Really?
Are you sure?
Your squad only just returned from the underwater temple
Yeah, I can handle it
Hell, right now I'm feeling damn near invincible
And besides
There's somebody I've been meaning to check up on
Well in that case I gladly accept your offer
I just wish I could go with you
That's not possible, sir
What if they're using this as an aversion to launch an attack on the capital?
Yes, yes
We mustn't be rash now
There's the King's safety to consider
It's settled then
Too bad I let Fenril go wander around town instead of coming with us
Lousy good-for-nothing's never where you need him
Someone must be talking about me
I wonder what they're saying
Oh, right! Official lovely lady sighting!
Hey there
I found the most beautiful girls in town
Care for a drink?
Captain Yummy!
Hmm?
Please take me with you, sir
Your arms are broken
Even if I can't fight, maybe I can help evacuate people
I do want him to rack up some battlefield experience, but still
Someone with your injuries would only hold me back, so you're gonna have to sit this one out at the base
But Captain!
As his superior, I'm willing to accompany him and make sure he's unharmed
You'd do that for me?
What do you say? Will that work?
Oh really? You're volunteering, Charmy?
Fine! Then I guess you idiots can come with me
Where the hell is Fenril?
Awesome! Thank you, sir!
Thank you, sir!
Alright! I'll get to see my Prince of Confucius!
Okay, you know
I'm coming
My, that's very impressive
He's tearing the enemy apart
And he's only going to get stronger
It's hard to believe a commoner has come so far within our ranks when he hasn't even been with us a year
His progress is staggering
Now, what do you say we go out there and join our newest recruit, Longris?
Absolutely, sir
By the time we're done, those Diamond Kingdom mages will regret ever setting foot in the country
radio
And thanks to all the joy of our nextcompass
For hours
For hours, lately
I've been crying for hours, baby
I wish you were here
The pain's gone
You know you're not alone
Cause we are perfect as four
離れ離れても
繋がるよ within me
いつも様に
私がいるから
Close side of me
And I'll clover for you
君に行こう
The Vow
Hey, you know it's been a while, huh?
It seems like you've gotten a lot stronger, though
Of course I have
I'm going to be the strongest of them all
Do you remember that vow we made when we were kids?
That we were gonna fight to see who will become the Wizard King?
Oh, that vow?
It was ages ago, I'd totally forgotten
Alright, quit trying to play it cool
So what are you up to tomorrow, anyway?
You gotta work?
Tomorrow?
That's too far in the future to say for sure
Seriously, quit trying to play it cool, you know
Hold on
You know?
Is that really my name?
But I don't know anything
It's all a blank what happened to me
You mean you're not just playing it cool?
What's wrong, you know?
We'll see you again soon for more fun-filled episodes of Black Clover
The Diamond Kingdom's attacking us and the Golden Dawn's been deployed to fight them?
Oh well, just let them handle it then
Black Clover episode 52
Whoever's strongest wins
Wait, Asta went too?
No problem